A Register of the Albert J. and Roberta Wohlstetter Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Photographs, 1964-1995. (Box 813)
  - Seven postcards of scenes in Wisconsin and Mexico, including depictions of murals by Orozco (Folder 813: 24)
  - Three prints depicting drawings by Odile Redon, probably relating to Roberta Wohlstetter's dissertation and Mellarmé's Igitur and Un Coup de Dés (Folder 813: 25)
  - Fifty-nine prints and five postcards depicting scenes from Hamlet illustrated by Eugène Delacroix, relating to Roberta Wohlstetter's dissertation on Hamlet figures (Folder 813: 26-27)
    Includes notes by Roberta Wohlstetter(?) and letter from Elizabeth Parker, Fogg Art Museum, Harvard University
- Microfilm, 1951-1952. (Box 814)
  One reel of filmed records from the National Archives concerning the Military Armistice Conference, Panmunjon, Korea, 1951 December 4 - 1952 January 7
- CLOSED (Box 815-821)
- Videotapes, 1976-1995. (Box 822)
  Five videotape recordings, comprising one speech and a television appearance by Albert Wohlstetter, and a program about the KGB
  - Two videotapes of a speech by Albert Wohlstetter, "Spreading the Bomb without Quite Breaking the Rules," Argonne National Laboratory, Argonne, Illinois, 1976 October. (Folder 822: 1-2)
    The second videotape is of an open discussion following the speech
  - One videotape of an appearance by Albert Wohlstetter on Japanese television, in conjunction with a conference on the issue of Okinawa, 1995 (Folder 822: 3)
  - Two videotapes consisting of a two-part program, "The KGB Connection,", n.d. (Box-folder 823: 1-2)
- Maps, 1953-1995 (Box 824)
  Includes maps relating to the Dayton Agreement and the conflict in Bosnia and Herzegovina
  - Taiwan, n.d. (Folder 824: 1)
  - Teheran, n.d. (Folder 824: 2)
  - United States (American Airlines routes), n.d. (Folder 824: 3)
  - Havana, 1953 (Folder 824: 4)
  - Japan, 1953 (Folder 824: 5)
  - Taiwan, 1964 (Folder 824: 6)
  - Central Japan, 1970 (Folder 824: 7)
  - South Korea, 1970 (Folder 824: 8)
  - South Korea, 1972 (Folder 824: 9)
  - Photocopies of maps of the Former Yugoslav republics, with holograph markings of force dispositions of belligerent parties, 1990-1991. (Folder 824: 10)
    22 sheets, and one folder of explanatory materials, with map scales
  - "Ethnic Map of the Republic of Croatia and of the Republic of Bosnia and Herzegovina,", 1991(?) (Folder 824: 11)
  - "Energy in the Newly Independent States of Eurasia,", 1992 (Folder 824: 12)
    (two copies)
  - Bosnia and Herzegovina, 1993 (Folder 824: 13)
  - Bosnia and Herzegovina, 1995. (Folder 824: 14)
    Includes detailed information concerning air space restrictions
  - Croatia, 1995 (Folder 824: 15)
  - "Dayton Agreement and Cease-Fire Lines, 24 November 1995." Refers to treaty concerning Bosnia and Herzegovina, with inset detail of its application in Sarajevo (Folder 824: 16)
- Memorabilia, 1984. (Box 825)
  Two plaques given to Albert Wohlstetter on the occasion of his keynote address at West Point, 1984 November 14
- Card File, n.d. (Box 826-830)
  Notes, largely pertaining to the research interests of Albert Wohlstetter, including extensive bibliographic information about writings by others in the fields of nuclear research and nuclear strategy
- Oversize Materials, 1930-1989. (Box 831)
  Blueprints, transparencies of maps and charts, posters, and printed matter
  - Blueprints, including technical data, for a house designed by the General Panel Corporation, 1947
  - Transparencies, 1967-1989. (Box 832-835)
    Maps and charts used for presentations, principally in relation to contractual work involving PanHeuristics. Includes displays of contingency plans involving American and other NATO military forces, as well as anticipated strategies of their Soviet counterparts
  - Posters, n.d. (Box 836)
    One poster displaying chair styles in the collection of the Vitra Design Museum, Weil am Rhein, Germany, and one poster showing artificial satellites and their orbits
  - Printed matter. Serial issues, 1930-1970 (Box 837)
- CLOSED (Box 838-857)